<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CAPACITE_LAB4</string>
    <string-array name="Name">
        <item>Cupcake</item>
        <item>Donut</item>
        <item>Eclair</item>
        <item>Froyo</item>
        <item>Gingerbread</item>
        <item>Honeycomb</item>
        <item>Ice Cream Sandwich</item>
        <item>Jelly Bean</item>
        <item>Kitkat</item>
        <item>Lollipop</item>
        <item>Marshmallow</item>
        <item>Nougat</item>
        <item>Oreo</item>
        <item>Pie</item>
        <item>10</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="Version">
        <item>1.5</item>
        <item>1.6</item>
        <item>2.0 - 2.1</item>
        <item>2.2 - 2.2.3</item>
        <item>2.3 - 2.3.7</item>
        <item>3.0 - 3.2.6</item>
        <item>4.0 - 4.0.4</item>
        <item>4.1 - 4.3.1</item>
        <item>4.4 - 4.4.4</item>
        <item>5.0 - 5.1.1</item>
        <item>6.0 - 6.0.1</item>
        <item>7.0 - 7.1.2</item>
        <item>8.0 - 8.1</item>
        <item>9.0</item>
        <item>10.0</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="ReleaseDate">
        <item>April 27, 2009</item>
        <item>September 15, 2009</item>
        <item>October 26, 2009</item>
        <item>May 20, 2010</item>
        <item>December 06, 2010</item>
        <item>February 22, 2011</item>
        <item>October 18, 2011</item>
        <item>July 09, 2012</item>
        <item>October 31, 2013</item>
        <item>November 12, 2014</item>
        <item>October 05, 2015</item>
        <item>August 22, 2016</item>
        <item>August 21, 2017</item>
        <item>August 06, 2018</item>
        <item>September 03, 2019</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="API">
        <item>3</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>5 - 7</item>
        <item>8</item>
        <item>9 - 10</item>
        <item>11 - 13</item>
        <item>14 - 15</item>
        <item>16 - 18</item>
        <item>19 - 20</item>
        <item>21 - 22</item>
        <item>23</item>
        <item>24 - 25</item>
        <item>26 - 27</item>
        <item>28</item>
        <item>29</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="Trivia">
        <item>Android "Cupcake" is the third version of Android developed by Google, a major platform release deployable to Android-powered handsets starting in April 2009, that is no longer supported.</item>
        <item>Android "Donut" is the fourth version of the open source Android mobile operating system developed by Google that is no longer supported.</item>
        <item>Android "Eclair" is a codename of the Android mobile operating system developed by Google and the fifth operating system for Android, and for the no-longer supported versions 2.0 to 2.1.</item>
        <item>Android "Froyo" is the sixth version of Android and is a codename of the Android mobile operating system developed by Google, spanning versions between 2.2 and 2.2.3. Those versions are no longer supported. It was unveiled on May 20, 2010, during the Google I/O 2010 conference.</item>
        <item>Android "Gingerbread" is the seventh version of Android, a codename of the Android mobile operating system developed by Google and released in December 2010, for versions that are no longer supported.</item>
        <item>Android "Honeycomb" is the codename for the eighth version of Android, designed for devices with larger screen sizes, particularly tablets. It is no longer supported. Honeycomb debuted with the Motorola Xoom in February 2011.</item>
        <item>Unveiled on October 19, 2011, Android 4.0 builds upon the significant changes made by the tablet-only release Android Honeycomb, in an effort to create a unified platform for both smartphones and tablets.</item>
        <item>Android "Jelly Bean" is the tenth version of Android and the codename given to three major point releases of the Android mobile operating system developed by Google, spanning versions between 4.1 and 4.3.1.</item>
        <item>Android "KitKat" is a codename for the Android mobile operating system and the eleventh version of Android. Unveiled on September 3, 2013, KitKat focused primarily on optimizing the operating system for improved performance on entry-level devices with limited resources.</item>
        <item>Android "Lollipop" is the fifth major version of the Android mobile operating system developed by Google, spanning versions between 5.0 and 5.1.1.</item>
        <item>Android "Marshmallow" is the sixth major version of the Android operating system and the 13th version of Android. First released as a beta build on May 28, 2015, it was officially released on October 5, 2015, with Nexus devices being the first to receive the update.</item>
        <item>Android "Nougat" is the seventh major version and 14th original version of the Android operating system. First released as an alpha test version on March 9, 2016, it was officially released on August 22, 2016, with Nexus devices being the first to receive the update. </item>
        <item>Android "Oreo" is the eighth major release and the 15th version of the Android mobile operating system. It was first released as an alpha quality developer preview in March 2017 and released to the public on August 21, 2017.</item>
        <item>Android Pie is the ninth major release and the 16th version of the Android mobile operating system. It was first released as a developer preview on March 7, 2018, and released publicly on August 6, 2018.</item>
        <item>Android 10 is the tenth major release and the 17th version of the Android mobile operating system. It was released on September 3, 2019.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
